<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-09-15T01:34:18-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Make Tech Work for Workers</title><author><name>The John Henry Committee</name></author><entry><title type="html">Introducing the John Henry Committee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025-09-15-introducing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introducing the John Henry Committee" /><published>2025-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2025-09-15T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/introducing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025-09-15-introducing/"><![CDATA[<p>The John Henry Committee is a collection of tech workers and
organizers drawn from a range of groups and organizations, including <a href="https://www.amazonclimatejustice.org/">Amazon Employees
for Climate Justice</a>, the
<a href="https://nytimesguild.org/">Times Tech Guild</a>,
<a href="https://turkopticon.net/">Turkopticon</a>,  workers organized with
<a href="https://code-cwa.org/">Code-CWA</a>, as well as
<a href="https://www.dair-institute.org/">DAIR</a>,  <a href="https://techworkerscoalition.org">Tech Workers
Coalition</a>, and <a href="https://collectiveaction.tech/">Collective Action
in Tech</a>. We assembled together
because we recognized the wide range of tech employeers rolling out AI
projects and mandates over the head of and without the input of their
workers. Even worse, they have been using these initiatives as a way
to attack our working conditions – instituting speedups, justifying
layoffs and headcount reductions, and and degrading the quality of our
products.</p>

<p>We know from our experience as organizers that workers are not
helpless in the face of these initiatives – we have the tools to
demand our seat at the table, and our say in how technology is
implemented and deployed in our workplaces. We believe every employer
with new technology mandates can and should be answered with organized
groups of workers who can ensure we get our collective say. This
project is a place for us to assemble information and resources to
help take a stand.</p>

<p>If you would like to get in touch or get involved, please reach out to
us at <a href="mailto:johnhenry@techworkerscoalition.org">johnhenry@techworkerscoalition.org</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>The John Henry Committee</name></author><category term="meta" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The John Henry Committee is a collection of tech workers and organizers drawn from a range of groups and organizations, including Amazon Employees for Climate Justice, the Times Tech Guild, Turkopticon, workers organized with Code-CWA, as well as DAIR, Tech Workers Coalition, and Collective Action in Tech. We assembled together because we recognized the wide range of tech employeers rolling out AI projects and mandates over the head of and without the input of their workers. Even worse, they have been using these initiatives as a way to attack our working conditions – instituting speedups, justifying layoffs and headcount reductions, and and degrading the quality of our products.]]></summary></entry></feed>